Guide to the Urban League of Portland Records 1910-2014
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections & Archives Research Center
Urban League of Portland Records
1910-2014
1940-2014
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections & Archives Research Center 121 The Valley Library Oregon State University Corvallis, OR 97331-4501 Phone: 541-737-2075 Email: scarc@oregonstate.edu Web: http://scarc.library.oregonstate.edu
Urban League of Portland (Portland, Or.)
MSS UrbanLeague
35 cubic feet, including 6200 photographs, 30 sound recordings, and 125 videotapes 34 boxes, including 3 oversize boxes
650 Mbytes 251 files
The Urban League of Portland Records document the administration and programs of the League from its founding in Portland, Oregon, in 1945. The Records reflect the League’s outreach to the community through various programs and activities, fund-raising, interaction with the National Urban League, and African American life in Portland. The collection includes extensive paper records as well as visual documentation in the form of photographs, videotapes, and sound recordings.
Historical Note:
The Urban League of Portland was established in 1945 as an affiliate of the National Urban League. It is a non-profit, community-based organization whose mission has been to "enable African Americans to secure economic self-reliance, parity and power, and civil rights". The League has emphasized educational opportunity for African Americans and other youth, advocated for fair housing laws, and offered employment assistance.
The Urban League of Portland Records consist of records generated by the League and its board, officers, staff, and affiliated organizations. The records document the administration of the organization and reflect the League's outreach to the community through various programs and activities, fund-raising, interaction with the National Urban League, and African American life in Portland. The subject files constitute the bulk of these materials and include information regarding housing, history of the League, minorities in business, urban renewal programs, various events and programs, education, and different League centers and services. The reports include annual and presidential reports as well as reports on race relations in Portland, African American children in Portland, and Northeast Portland neighborhood revitalization. The publications include League newsletters, brochures, and reports on various topics from the National Urban League office and branches in other cities. The records include constitutions and bylaws, committee information, correspondence, financial statements, surveys, event materials and press releases, meeting minutes, newspaper clippings, photograph albums, photographs, posters, scrapbooks, sound recordings, videotapes, award plaques, and a building plaque.
The photographs include prints, negatives, slides, and digital photographs and are only minimally arranged and described. The images, which date from the 1940s to 2005, depict League meetings, League representatives meeting with Oregon politicians, community events, League directors and board members, and League staff at National Urban League conferences. The images also document League outreach events such as job fairs, activities at the Multicultural Senior Center, programs at Okley Green Middle School, and fields trips for students to Willamette University and other locations. Many of the photographs are arranged chronologically.
The videotapes and sound recordings primarily document League events such as conference presentations, annual dinners, workshops, and award ceremonies in the 1990s, with a few recordings made in the 1980s. The sound recordings also include public service announcements and broadcasts of radio programs.
Collection is open for research.
The Urban League of Portland Records are arranged in 3 subgroups: Subgroup 1. Records, 1910-2014; Subgroup 2. Photographs and Visual Materials, 1945-2005; and Subgroup 3. Audio and Video Materials, 1962-2003. Subgroup 1 (Records) consists of 8 series: 1. Administration, 1947-2010; 2. Committees, 1947-2009; 3. Correspondence, 1977-1998; 4. Financials, 1951-2004; 5. Meeting Minutes, 1945-2003; 6. Newspaper Clippings, 1944-2013; 7. Reports and Publications, 1940-2014; and 8. Subject Files, 1910-2013. Subgroup 2 (Photographs and Visual Materials) consists of 4 series: 1. Photographs, 1945-2005; 2. Posters, 1997-1999; 3. Scrapbooks and Photograph Albums, 1991-1996; and 4. Plaques, 1984-1990. Subgroup 3 (Audio and Video Materials) consists of 2 series: 1. Video, 1981-2003 and 2. Audio, 1962-1998.
The records were donated by the Urban League of Portland to the University Archives and the Special Collections & Archives Research Center in several accessions from 2007 through 2014.
This collection is a component of the Oregon Multicultural Archives, which also includes the Harold C. Williams Papers. Meeting minutes, newsletters, reports, constitutions, and memos are available online. Selected images are available online in the Oregon Multicultural Archives Digital Collection. Oral history interviews pertaining to the Urban Leage of Portland are part of the Oregon Multicultural Archives Oral History Collection (OH 18).
See also: The Urban League of Portland Digital Collection, a site providing access to the Urban League of Portland Records guide, digitized content from the collection, and historical background on the organization.
National Urban League.; Portland Public Schools (Or.)
Portland (Or.)--Race relations.
African Americans--Oregon--Portland.; Older people--Services for--Oregon--Portland.
Born digital.; Film negatives.; Photograph albums.; Photographic prints.; Scrapbooks.; Slides.; Sound recordings.; Video recordings.
African Americans; Children and Youth; City and Town Life; Civic Activism; Civil Rights; Elementary and Secondary Education; Portland; Artifacts; Electronic Records; Moving Images; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Sound Recordings
- Records, 1910-2014; Subgroup 1; 11.8 cubic feet
  Subgroup 1 consists of records assembled by the Urban League of Portland and created by the Urban League of Portland, the National Urban League, affiliates thereof, and community organizations. These materials include newspaper clippings, correspondence, and reports and publications. A few photographs are also dispersed throughout. The majority of these files reflect the organization's actions and missions both internally and externally, leadership, programs, projects, centers, issues, and its interaction with the community. The bulk of the materials are from the 1940s through early 2000s. Meeting minutes, newsletters, reports, constitutions, and memos are available online.
  - Administration, 1947-2010; Series 1
    Series 1 consists of information pertaining to the Urban League of Portland's Board of Directors. Materials include correspondence, membership lists, member evaluations, guideline packets, and official statements. Both board members and staff are represented in this series. While several specific staff members are highlighted, there is also information pertaining to staff members in general and evaluations thereof. The Administration records also consist of organizational charts, handbooks, constitutions, and resolutions. The materials in this series were produced both by the Urban League of Portland and the National Urban League. The Urban League of Portland also created a handbook that provides information on the CEO, the organization's structure, and position descriptions for staff.
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1965 (Box-folder 1.1)
    - Board of Directors, 1977-2004; Sub-Series 1
      - Appointments, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1.2)
      - Members, 1977-2004; 2 folders (Box-folder 1.3-1.4)
      - Member Surveys, 1983 (Box-folder 1.5)
      - New Member Packet, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 1.6)
      - New Member Selection, 1995 (Box-folder 1.7)
      - Responsibilities and Evaluations, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 1.8)
      - Retreat, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 1.9)
    - CEO, Margaret Carter, 2000 (Box-folder 1.10)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1983-2004; 2 folders (Box-folder 1.11-1.12)
    - General Staff Retreat, 1997 (Box-folder 1.13)
    - Handbooks and Manuals, 1982-1999; Sub-Series 2
      - Affiliate Operations Manual, 1982-1987; 2 folders (Box-folder 1.14-1.15)
      - Manual of Standards, 1985 (Box-folder 1.16)
      - Personnel Policies, 1999 (Box-folder 1.17)
    - Membership Drives, 1969-1998 (Box-folder 1.18)
    - Mission and Philosophy Statement, 1985 (Box-folder 1.19)
    - Organizational Charts, 1975-2001 (Box-folder 1.20)
    - Personnel, 1947-2010; Sub-Series 3
      - Edwin Carlos Berry, 1955 (Box-folder 1.21)
      - Ralph Bunche, 1949 (Box-folder 1.22)
      - Clifford Campbell, 1948 (Box-folder 1.23)
      - Lawrence Dark, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 1.24)
      - E. Shelton Hill, 1947-1974 (Box-folder 1.25)
        includes 27 photographs
      - Faye Lyday, 1967-2010 (Box-folder 1.26)
      - Darryl S. Tukufu, 1993 (Box-folder 1.27)
      - Ron Sykes, 1985 (Box-folder 1.28)
    - Resolutions, 1986-2000 (Box-folder 1.29)
    - Staff, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 1.30)
    - Urban League Affiliates, circa 1970s-1998 (Box-folder 1.31)
    - Urban League of Portland Overview, 1984; 2 folders (Box-folder 1.32-1.33)
  - Committees, 1947-2009; Series 2
    Series 2 consists of the records of external and internal committees. The external committees are those outside the Urban League organization with which the Urban League of Portland participated, was a member, or collaborated. In some cases, the files for external committees consist solely of information that the Urban League gathered, such as for the House Un-American Activities Committee. The internal committees were established by the Urban League of Portland or the National Urban League. The internal committee records document the Equal Opportunities Day Dinner, nominations, membership drives, and administration and functioning of the organization.
    - External Committees, 1947-2009; Sub-Series 1
      - American Friends Service Committee, 1947-1967 (Box-folder 1.34)
      - American Jewish Committee, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 1.35)
      - American Veterans Committee, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 1.36)
      - Citizens' Committee (Portland, Oakland, CA, New York), 1963-1970 (Box-folder 1.37)
      - Commission on Human Relations (Philadelphia, Ohio, Chicago, Oklahoma), 1964-1969 (Box-folder 1.38)
      - Committee for Economic Development, 1968 (Box-folder 1.39)
      - Council on the Aging (National, New York, Maryland, Multnomah County), 1958-1969 (Box-folder 1.40)
      - General Advisory Committee for Social Work, 1965 (Box-folder 1.41)
      - Governor's State Committee on Children and Youth, 1964 (Box-folder 1.42)
      - Metropolitan Interfaith Commission on Race, 1963 (Box-folder 1.43)
      - Multnomah County's Human Relations, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 1.44)
      - National Committee for Support of Public Schools, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 1.45)
      - Oregon Committee on Legal Termination of Pregnancy, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 1.46)
      - Oregon Council on Civil Rights, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 1.47)
      - Portland Commission on Intergroup Relations, 1953-1968 (Box-folder 2.1)
      - Portland Metropolitan Steering Committee of the Economic Opportunity Act, 1966-1973; 2 folders (Box-folder 2.2-2.3)
      - Public Affairs Committee (Portland), 1968 (Box-folder 2.4)
      - State Manpower and Training Advisory Committee, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 2.5)
      - House Un-American Activities Committee, undated, 1947 (Box-folder 2.6)
      - Youth Development Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 2.7)
    - Internal Committees, 1960-1999; Sub-Series 2
      - Advisory Task Force on Senior Affairs, 1987 (Box-folder 2.8)
      - CEO Search Committee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2.9)
      - Committee Assignments, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 2.10)
      - Committee Responsibilities and Functions, circa 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 2.11)
      - Executive Committee, 1960-1983 (Box-folder 2.12)
      - Finance Committee, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 2.13)
      - Fundraising Committee, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 2.14)
      - Job Development and Employment Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2.15)
      - National Urban League's Commerce and Industry Council, 1961 (Box-folder 2.16)
      - Nominating Committee, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 2.17)
      - Personnel Committee, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 2.18)
      - Program and Planning Committee, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 2.19)
      - Quality of Life and Equality Committee, 1998 (Box-folder 2.20)
      - Technology Committee, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 2.21)
      - Vision Committees, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 2.22)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1998; Series 3
    Series 3 consists of correspondence to and from the Urban League of Portland, the National Urban League, and several Urban League Affiliates. Topics include finances, the Equal Opportunities Day Dinner, resignations, meeting notices, and threats to the Urban League.
    - James O. Brooks (Executive Director), 1977 (Box-folder 2.23)
    - Budget Deficit, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2.24)
    - Herb Cawthorne (President and CEO), 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box-folder 2.25-2.26)
    - Medical/Dental Plan, 1988 (Box-folder 2.27)
    - Memos and Incident Reports, 1998 (Box-folder 2.28)
    - National Urban League Headquarters, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 2.29)
    - Performance Assessment, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2.30)
    - Linda Rasmussen (Board Chairperson), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 2.31)
    - General, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 2.32)
    - General, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2.33)
    - General, 1987; 2 folders (Box-folder 2.34-2.35)
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2.36)
  - Financials, 1951-2004; Series 4
    Series 4 consists of the Urban League of Portland's financial information, including grants, donor information, scholarship recipients, scholarship funds, account ledgers, financial statements, and audits.
    - Account Ledger, 1961 (Box-item 3.1)
    - Account Ledger, 1963 (Box-item 3.2)
    - Account Ledger, 1964 (Box-item 3.3)
    - Account Ledger, 1965 (Box-item 4.1)
    - Account Ledger, 1965 (Box-item 4.2)
    - Account Ledger, 1965-1966 (Box-item 4.3)
    - Account Ledger, 1966 (Box-item 4.4)
    - Account Ledger, 1966-1967 (Box-item 4.5)
    - Account Ledger, 1967 (Box-item 3.4)
    - Budgets, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 5.1)
    - Donors, 1952-2001 (Box-folder 5.2)
    - Dues to the Council of Board Presidents, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 5.3)
    - Financial Reports, 1986-1998; 2 folders (Box-folder 5.4-5.5)
    - Financial Statements with Auditors' Report, 1972-2004; 2 folders (Box-folder 5.6-5.7)
    - Fundraising, 1985-2000 (Box-folder 5.8)
    - Fundraising: Capital Fund Drive, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5.9)
    - Grants, 1985-2001; Sub-Series 1
      - Borden Corporation, 1995 (Box-folder 5.10)
      - Cultural Leadership Program Grant Proposal, 1994 (Box-folder 5.11)
      - Gates Foundation, 2000 (Box-folder 5.12)
      - Meyer Memorial Trust, 1992-1996; 2 folders (Box-folder 5.13-5.14)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1995 (Box-folder 5.15)
      - National Grant for Service on MLK Holiday, 1997 (Box-folder 5.16)
      - Northwest Area Foundation, 1996 (Box-folder 5.17)
      - Oregon Community Foundation, 1997 (Box-folder 5.18)
      - United Way of the Columbia-Willamette, 1985-2001; 2 folders (Box-folder 5.19-5.20)
    - Insurance Policies, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5.21)
    - Scholarships, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 5.22)
    - Scholarships: Debnam Scholarship, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5.23)
    - Scholarships: Will C. Davis Scholarship, 1951-1957 (Box-folder 5.24)
    - Tax Exemption Information, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 5.25)
    - United States Treasury Reimbursement, 1997 (Box-folder 5.26)
    - Will C. Davis Loan Fund, 1951-1956; 2 folders (Box-folder 5.27-5.28)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1945-2003; Series 5; 43 folders
    Series 5 consists of meeting minutes from the Urban League of Portland's Board of Directors, who met monthly. The dates of these meeting minutes range from 1945 to 1949 and 1964 to 2003. Most of the materials in this series are the actual meeting minutes. However, meeting agendas are also included in these materials.
    - Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, Undated (Box-folder 6.1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1945-1949, 1964-2003 (Box-folder 6.2-8.4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1944-2013; Series 6
    Series 6 consists of newspaper clippings collected by the Urban League of Portland. Most of these materials are arranged by decade. Some of the files are arranged by subject, as organized by Urban League staff. Topics include black cultural leaders, the organization itself, athletics, and issues of concern for communities of color.
    - General, 1944-2013, undated; 14 folders (Box-folder 8.5-8.19)
    - General: Oversize Photocopies, 1942-1971 (Box-folder 14.1)
    - General: Scrapbook, 1953-1980 (Box-folder 14.2)
      Primarily clippings from the mid-1950s.
    - Subject, 1946-1979; Sub-Series 1
      Original folder titles are used and enclosed in quotation marks.
      - "Adam Clayton Powell", 1969-1972 (Box-folder 9.1)
      - "Afro-American Culture", circa 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 9.2)
      - "Aid to Dependent Children Mothers", 1972 (Box-folder 9.3)
      - "Albina Citizens Together (Community Action Center)", 1971 (Box-folder 9.4)
      - "Albina Community Conference", 1960 (Box-folder 9.5)
      - "Albina Corporation", 1971-1972 (Box-folder 9.6)
      - "Albina Housing", 1961-1963 (Box-folder 9.7)
      - "Albina Misc.", 1960 (Box-folder 9.8)
      - "All Negro Towns", 1947 (Box-folder 9.9)
      - "Arthur Fletcher", 1970-1972 (Box-folder 9.10)
      - "Assassinations/Killings", 1972 (Box-folder 9.11)
      - "Black Caucus", 1972 (Box-folder 9.12)
      - "Black Militants", 1971 (Box-folder 9.13)
      - "Black Monitor", 1979 (Box-folder 9.14)
      - "Black Panthers", 1967-1971 (Box-folder 9.15)
      - "Boise School Problem", 1973 (Box-folder 9.16)
      - "Busing", 1972 (Box-folder 9.17)
      - "Cheryl James Case", 1972 (Box-folder 9.18)
      - "Civil Rights", 1969 (Box-folder 9.19)
      - "Clara Peoples", 1972 (Box-folder 9.20)
      - "Communist Party of Oregon", 1961-1964 (Box-folder 9.21)
      - "Concentrated Employment Program", 1969 (Box-folder 9.22)
      - "Dr. DeNorval Unthank", 1970-1971 (Box-folder 9.23)
      - "Dr. Martin Luther King", 1961-1976 (Box-folder 9.24)
      - "Freedom Riders", 1961 (Box-folder 9.25)
      - "'Green Thumb Project' Albina", 1969-1970 (Box-folder 9.26)
      - "Imamu Sukumu", 1972 (Box-folder 9.27)
      - "Joan Little Case", 1974-1975 (Box-folder 9.28)
      - "Leadership Conference on Civil Rights", 1970 (Box-folder 9.29)
      - "Mr. Ira C. Keller", 1972 (Box-folder 9.30)
      - "Muslims", 1961-1963 (Box-folder 9.31)
      - "NAACP", 1955-1972 (Box-folder 9.32)
      - "NAACP Portland Branch", 1969 (Box-folder 9.33)
      - Negro in the Armed Services, 1946-1957 (Box-folder 9.34)
      - "Negro Mothers", 1946-1957 (Box-folder 9.35)
      - "Negro Teachers", 1946-1957 (Box-folder 9.36)
      - "Negroes and Vice", 1953-1959 (Box-folder 9.37)
      - "Negroes and Progress", 1956 (Box-folder 9.38)
      - "Negroes in the Court of Law", 1949-1966 (Box-folder 9.39)
      - "Negroes in Politics and the Negro Vote", 1956-1969 (Box-folder 9.40)
      - "Negroes in Sports", 1947-1957 (Box-folder 9.41)
      - "Newgate", 1969 (Box-folder 9.42)
      - "Noted Negroes in News", 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9.43)
      - "Office of Economic Opportunity, 1969 (Box-folder 9.44)
      - "Opportunities Industrial Center", 1968 (Box-folder 9.45)
      - "Oregon Politicians", 1956-1966 (Box-folder 9.46)
      - "Outstanding Americans", 1948-1956 (Box-folder 9.47)
      - "Paul Robeson", 1946-1956 (Box-folder 9.48)
      - "Portland Public Schools", 1969-1972 (Box-folder 9.49)
      - "Portland Youth Development Comm.", 1970 (Box-folder 9.50)
      - "Race Relations", 1961 (Box-folder 9.51)
      - "Republican Party", 1970-1972 (Box-folder 9.52)
      - "Riots (Cities, Districts)", 1969 (Box-folder 9.53)
      - "SATCHMO Louis Armstrong", 1971 (Box-folder 9.54)
      - "School Boundaries", 1957-1970 (Box-folder 9.55)
      - "School Integration", 1961-1969 (Box-folder 9.56)
      - "Southern Christian Leadership Conference", 1970 (Box-folder 9.57)
      - "Summer Student Program", 1969 (Box-folder 9.58)
      - "United States Air Corps, 1972 (Box-folder 9.59)
      - "Urban Coalition", 1968-1972 (Box-folder 9.60)
      - "Women's Forum and Moss-Adams Award Luncheon", 1973 (Box-folder 9.61)
      - "Women's Lib. Movement", 1972 (Box-folder 9.62)
  - Reports and Publications, 1940-2014; Series 7
    Series 7 consists of publications in the forms of bulletins, newsletters, pamphlets, and proposals. The producers of these materials include the National Urban League, the Urban League of Portland, other Urban League branches, and community clubs and organizations. The reports include internal and external reports that reflect topics ranging from routine updates, the goals of the CEO, social and economic problems, and race relations.
    - Bulletins: Portland City Club, 1957-1995 (Box-folder 9.63)
    - Bulletins: Urban League of Portland, 1976 (Box-folder 9.64)
    - Newsletters, 1967-2011; Sub-Series 1
      - Creating Community Solutions, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9.65)
      - The Drum, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 9.66)
      - The Multicultural Senior Center Newsletter, 1999-2005 (Box-folder 9.67)
      - National Urban League Newsletter, 1967 (Box-folder 9.68)
      - Our Children Our Destiny, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 9.69)
      - Update, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 9.70)
      - The Urban Express, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 9.71)
      - Urban League of Portland Newsletter, 1980 (Box-folder 9.72)
      - Urban News Monthly, 1977 (Box-folder 9.73)
      - The Urban Senior, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 9.74)
      - Urban Voice, 1998-2008 (Box-folder 9.75)
      - View, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 9.76)
    - News Releases, 1968-2003 (Box-folder 9.77)
    - Pamphlets (Outside Producers), 1950-1996 (Box-folder 9.78)
    - Pamphlets (Urban League Produced), 2010-2013 (Box-folder 9.79)
    - Plans/Proposals, 1964-2003; Sub-Series 2
      - "10 Year N/NE Portland Comeback Plan", 1988 (Box-folder 9.80)
      - Business Plan, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9.81)
      - "Cultural Diversity Plan", 1994 (Box-folder 9.82)
      - "Liberty City Renaissance", circa 1990 (Box-folder 9.83)
      - "Moving Forward, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 9.84)
      - "Needs Assessment 5 Year Plan, 1992-1997" (Box-folder 9.85)
      - "Statement of the Case for Increased Support of the Urban League of Portland", 1964 (Box-folder 9.86)
      - "Strategic Plan, 2003-2010" (Box-folder 9.87)
      - "Strategy for a More Effective Urban League Movement", 1985 (Box-folder 9.88)
    - Publications (Outside Producers), 1940-1958 (Box-folder 9.89)
    - Reports, 1945-2014; Sub-Series 3
      - Activity Reports, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 10.1)
      - Annual Reports, 1945-2012; 2 folders (Box-folder 10.2-10.3)
      - "Chattanooga: In Black and White", 1986 (Box-folder 10.4)
      - "National Urban League Guidelines for Self-Evaluation by Urban League Affiliates", 1986 (Box-folder 10.5)
      - Monthly Reports, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 10.6)
      - "National Priorities Report", 1984 (Box-folder 10.7)
      - PACT Business Report, 1964 (Box-folder 10.8)
      - Presidential Reports, 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box-folder 10.9-10.10)
      - "Profile of Urban League President and Affiliates", 1994 (Box-folder 10.11)
      - Quarterly Report, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 10.12)
      - "Report of the Dialogue on Race Relations", 1998 (Box-folder 10.13)
      - "Report on the Goals of the CEO", 1986 (Box-folder 10.14)
      - "Socio-Economic Problems Affecting the Negro-White Relationship, 1952 (Box-folder 10.15)